Hi, let's begin start this video. I got an anonymous tip that
Samann
In a in a hysterical state
asked RG to go after me IRL and
That's not I mean that's in real life, you know
And you oh, yeah, well, just so you listen oh it speaks for itself
I'm not sure if the person I
Don't know if the same person that this video. This is sent it to me. I think but it is a pack yourself up video
So you can have a look I watched some of it, let me see
We can just have a
a real look at insecure sad sad persons. Here we go this is on the pack
yourself up channel. It's about half an hour. Let's have a little look see.
Tiger is my how are you let's let's expose this fool
To see you things for being here
Okay
Let me finish, let me finish, let me finish, let me finish, let me finish, let me finish,
let me finish, let me finish, let me finish, let me finish, let me finish, let me finish,
Everyone knows this, nope, nope, before I went out chasing them.
I'm not okay. I won't let me finish. But let me finish. Let me finish. And I know
Stop asking like a fucking making monkey noises and have a conversation with me.
My nigga. My nigga. You don't want to have a conversation.
Shut the fuck up nigga. Damn. Let me talk.
Stop it with the big dog thing. Let me talk. Just stop it.
You're yelling on me nigga. You yelling on me. I gotta, I gotta mute you now. Like a little nigga.
I? Aim into your server first.
You're a little nigga. You're not letting me talk. So I gotta yell now.
You're a little nigga now let me let me talk nigga
You know what a weaponized retard is
You know what a recognize me three man shut the fuck up nigga shut the fuck up nigga. Let me talk
You said you didn't did it most recent time. I never said you doc's beta
Yeah, niggas is getting caught up and y'all niggas is outing y'all some I never put RG doc's beta
Never said that RG said anything to
I think Kate's whole point is if beta can forgive RG why not her
So, Eldo may be right on this one.
So, all right, if that's what Eldo's saying, shout out to Eldo.
I don't understand what you're not getting, said that.
N***a, shout out to Eldo now!
N***a, shout out to Eldo!
Don't be saved.
I'm just reading chat, dude.
N***a, I don't give up.
This is over nothing.
I don't give up for what it is.
You can't do this.
That's what it is.
I'm an old man, n***a.
You can't give up for what it is.
I'm an old man.
That's why I said I'm not a sheep, n***a.
I don't give up.
Oh, my God.
Shout out to Eldo now.
This is what's called recognizing a retard, same man.
Don't think you're fucking talking.
Chateaubo, Chateaubo.
I'm reading a content, I'll feed it again.
Chateaubo.
Shane, you're not going to let me speak.
I did what Shane Adams six three six two said. I think kids whole point is if Vita can forgive RG
Why not her? So Eldo may be right there. I don't know what Eldo said. I'm just repeating or excuse me
Why are you?
I just know Kate was holding next to down and she out of it out because a curse on Marie
I get an entire stream about it. All right. I didn't know never I did not know
That's what we first met
You don't remember that. You win RL on Vita? Never. Never.
She knows about it.
I don't care.
You're acting like you're breaking news.
You don't bring the RG on everything I want.
I don't care.
Vita will get you that upset till you go go RL on Vita.
That's weak to me.
That's weak.
Imagine we just talking about Doxon, but you doxon Vita,
but you don't know where it's going to take you.
Ahh!
Oh my god.
You're a weaponized reanarcher and it's hilarious.
Dude, that's what this is. You're being weaponized right now. This is not new news
I did a stream on it every day. Can you be to have talked and laughed about it?
Decided to be team Jimmy and it didn't work out in her face
Oh
Are you so fired up about our scene Jimmy how many y'all
Come on now we're gonna hate me. You know who kept the real know who kept the real on my mother that kept the real
That came over here. That's a art. That's a art vandalism. That's a fucking thing
Hate bonding with jimmy. Oh my god
If I was cool with jimmy that was gonna dox me y'all thought I was cool with jimmy
Absolutely jimmy's not a lot to have friends. We're very clear about that
Doxing people for what for for for Jimmy? Oh my god, who is firing you up, dude? It's so transparent
It's so fucking transparent right now. Someone is weaponizing a retard. Don't let yourself be
This is two years ago or a year ago at this point you're acting like breaking news all right
I didn't I didn't I didn't I didn't out the shit out take this or don't get mad at me. I did an entire stream about this
Countless times what are you on about is this like are you on that?
I just know my nigga, I don't need to go real life over words
Okay, why didn't you do this a year ago?
You're trying to tell me you didn't know
No, I'm not although I'm not gonna hit up KK. I still like Sam and I don't know what's up his ass with me right now
This is obviously so using him as a weaponized
On a hundred, I don't need you to like me nigga. I didn't start my fucking YouTube with you nigga. I've got my crew
This is all because I called my little friend, uh, juicing himself
I've got to stand alone and be a wolf than be so manipulative.
You're not doing this because it's huge, right?
You didn't let juice manipulate you.
It's being a weaponized beat, all right?
I don't need it.
All right, Catlin, Capri says,
but Sam, man, it's too dumb to see this.
Yeah, I don't care a fuck.
I
Even after this song and dance me and beat are still gonna be
About what happened to Eda, I enter it with me, Lady Bathory.
Oh my God, you let Elbow Docs, Lady Bathory, you forgot that?
You got a mouse pair and you got to get between me and Lady Bathory.
They're not the same nigga, Elbow. See how thick is that?
Yes sir.
Or you let Elbow Docs, you let Elbow do this, but you shot him out now.
I didn't let Elda do anything.
You said that to me.
Oh, yeah, well, she was upset and I made an obvious point that lots of people were digging.
Dude, someone is firing you up and it's hilarious to me.
Someone is using you as a weaponized retard and you're letting it happen.
All I know, all I know, Bita can get mad at all I want.
Bita can say anything or anybody can say anything.
I'm not going real life on niggas because I could have been did that.
Okay, and I'm not getting mad at where it's online.
Okay, God bless.
All right, good.
Are you done?
I didn't lie.
You didn't lie about what?
You heard Kate say something.
It got confused in your brain.
No, I didn't get confused.
I didn't say more.
She didn't get confused.
Everyone else used it for you.
There you go, real life on beta.
You say, yeah.
It happened a year ago, and me and
Okay, we got it in all of a sudden a year later. You're mad about it
I didn't fuck your mom. I don't know why you're upset
Year later
Yeah, you just get mad in doctrine
Exactly so you thought if I was cool with Jimmy you would have done me too nigga
Oh my god, you cool with Jimmy, now I gotta go real life.
100%.
What does the, what does the, what does that do to Jimmy?
Nothing.
You can't even speak fucking English.
Dude, why you don't do that?
You know who's still cool with Jimmy?
You know who's still cool with Jimmy's panel?
Q and, Q and Barry, why you don't say shit to them?
Neither of them are friends with Jimmy.
They still go on the panel.
Why are you acting like this is new information?
Is this your way of calling me out because I can't use it in self?
That's what this is. This, that's exactly what this is. It's time to get the logs off and go touch grass, damn it.
The way you're trying to make fucking enemies with everybody. You can't fight the world, dude.
All because I'm friends with people. All because I'm friends with Nita and Carl Chupin and Zell.
Polaris.
Fake enemies, they're fake friends. All day.
You have any real friends? You just have people you haven't autistically fought with yet.
Yeah, okay, mm-hmm. Hey RG all I know when if I argue with you and you cool with Kate
I'm not gonna look you up and send you shit
The Jimmy line has always been the Jimmy
Yeah, it's that dick. Yeah, not me. You're taking something that happened a fucking year
It's hilarious to me that you're letting someone manipulate you. I don't give a fuck
I'm glad you don't give a phone to everyone else.
No, no, no, that's just funny that people are in chat right now.
And they don't want you.
No, they don't want you.
You're getting circulated.
Like, I'm telling you, you take this shit too serious.
But let this just go awry.
Are you taking this serious?
I think it's cool.
With Jimmy, that's taking this shit seriously.
Go ahead.
You want to be friends with someone who sends his dick through a 17-year-old?
All right.
Why don't you be friends with Brandon Q, too?
Why don't you go be friends with Brandon Q, too?
All right.
So do that shit to Cy, because Cy said he want to fuck Brandon Q.
Again, that's not my problem.
Jimmy's my problem.
Exactly.
Jimmy's your problem.
So you select him with it.
All right, God.
Jesus Christ.
This is not new information, said Ed.
This is not new at all.
All right.
So do that shit to Cy, because he want to fuck Brandon Q.
No.
Because my deal is Jimmy.
That's that's why I like you I don't try to fight the entire world
Now you're thinking of fight with me for no reason at all. No fucking reason
Actually, there is a reason it's because I called use an in-self. That's why you're doing this
Retard put that on everything that I'm taking news battle for you
I have no idea who's firing you up. It's so
100%
You'd be looking up to me
Okay, by the way, that's a good point. Pay attention, Sam-Man is telling RG to go real life on psych.
Make a note of it, folks. Why didn't you hope that? Sam-Man is telling me to go real life on psyching.
I said, why you don't? I said, actually, why you don't?
Hello? Hello? Actually, why you don't? Why you don't?
You wind the tape. Hello? Why you don't?
I got the clip.
I ready to stay down is that what you chase people across, uh, you know, YouTube just like a monkey 24 seven
Why you tell me to go real life
You can
All day all day, this is hilarious dude hilarious
Hello, you worked yourself into a little tizzy.
You worked yourself into a little tizzy because of something that happened a year ago.
And you can be to have a laugh about it many times, all of a sudden you're angry about
it?
Come on.
Come on
Real life on beat up over words kiss the baby
I'll get so mad all that, but you don't see me go through life over some time.
Last night, Beto said she was going to dinner with her friend.
You ask, with you, you ask what time, you ask how long she's going to be.
You are controlling Beto.
You got called out for it.
You act like a shitless boyfriend.
When you actually go real life with some dumb shit, go ahead.
He's not allowed to have friends.
Simple as that.
Go ahead, okay.
We're done?
You've known this for a year, and you're crying about it now.
That's what I know.
That's what I want.
You're crying about it now.
A year later.
Why you let Jimmy on your panel?
Why you do this?
I didn't give a fuck.
A year on my panel. Did I was scared of y'all? I let Jimmy on my panel until I said not here
What is going on with you? Wow? Oh my god, don't let Jimmy sleep on your panel. Like I'll buddy buddy with the nigger
Can you mention by name, but all of a sudden you're fired up into a tizzy? I don't believe that
So last night, again, I'm gonna say it again, last night,
Bita said she was going out to deal with her friends.
You asked her who's she going with,
how long she was going to be, what time she's going,
that's called controlling, by the way.
You 100% do you try to control her panel, you control who goes on her panel, you don't think
Bita doesn't notice, you don't think Bita doesn't notice that you're trying to control everything
about her channel.
Dude, I wasn't the one who called it out yesterday.
You had people on your panel that called that out.
You do.
Everyone else sees it.
Why can't you?
Yeah, that's finally shut you up in it. It happened would go watch Peter stream from last night
She said she was going out with her friends
You gave her the whole fucking the the whole fucking 20 questions. Who you going out with you? How long you gonna be?
Yeah, how many people you want with which I'm gonna be back. That sounds like some good friend shit to me
But what do I know?
I didn't start this when you said it, and you picked the fight with me this morning.
No, no, no, I picked it up when he started, and I just finished it.
He needs it.
I picked up what big Ben started, and I finished it, nigga.
Enjoy your meal.
You didn't finish anything.
Enjoy your meal, nigga.
Screamed like a monkey for 20 minutes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Yeah
Let me talk
Excuse me little nigga, I gotta talk on my panel. It's funny big Ben talk this shit and want to strike me
But she's streaming me right now
Right now. I have no idea who
Imagine having a
What the fuck you even talking about
No, you are okay. Let's
I'm good. I gotta play my music. You're done. You go go go to big band channel
I'm done with you. You go
Person to believes there's actually a grace because that's how dumb he is
That's the problem
I didn't even mention you. I don't need I don't you're a
When my eyes don't go, I go!
You don't understand that?
I'll go at you nigga!
I don't need people!
Woo!
That should sound like high school.
Can you tell me what this is about, really?
Please, can we get to the bottom of this and move on?
You go go to fucking Big Band and finish your combo, nigga.
You're excused.
I'm just asking what this is.
I got time to play my music.
You're excused, my nigga.
Again, what is this really about, so we can settle it?
You're excused.
Hello?
If you have to make content out of this, you, sir, are desperate for content.
That's a big bend out in this shit out, nigga.
Big bend out, not me.
What?
What out?
You're the are you the only person in this entire community that didn't know that me and beta had a falling out when we first met I
Don't know if there's IRL at or not you have to ask her I don't
Making shit up in your monkey head
I'm good. You just admitted.
Admitted what?
I ain't got to stand on something, man.
The person who fucked with me the last time was J-Dog.
This has been cleared up for months.
You bragged about it.
Don't hide this.
Dude, this is so fucking dumb.
You are so retarded.
You are so retarded
People say the same is retard I go doys
Take my mask look take my mask from the floor it slipped on the floor
You guys don't, you have someone fucking gassing you up over each shit.
I just see it, baby.
100 percent.
And I'm going to call it out.
What fordiness?
Dude, this is nothing new.
Ask Bita.
We laugh about this. I don't know if someone went real life on or not
But me and Bita had a massive falling out when we first met we overcame that and became friends
I'm sorry. If your insecurity can't handle it. I didn't say nothing
When Rob rocks, hold on see that's when I hate when you play that shit when Rob
Hold on. Hold on. No, you trying to make a point like I'm chair with you and B to do when Rob
Why you don't let me finish my nigga, you said I care about you and beta when Rob Ross joined the panel
I jumped the fuck off because you know what Ron is Ron was right about the Rob rocks. You don't want to cover that
Shut the fuck up my nigga, let me talk when you said I get in between you'll be the when Rob rocks is on panel
I'm be the I have to fuck off and let y'all do what y'all want to do
All the time. It's wrong to be one want to cook Rob Rods. I don't
Know let me you said I jump in y'all beef when I ever jump about Rob Rods and y'all beef never there was no beef
That was in
Imaginary, you know who Daria's
That was Rob Rex's ex-girlfriend who happens to be a friend of mine.
I don't want to talk about that. Let Ron cook that.
Well, that's what my point is. Exactly.
I was talking to her. She's a friend of mine, as is Rob, right?
I was on her panel talking about it, and Ron fucking popped up.
Ha-ha! Beedah's a snake. It was covering for Rob.
Daria looked at her. It was like, who are you and what are you talking about?
I had to explain to Daria like you.
Okay, you have beef snickers?
I'm not saying you did.
I didn't bring up the wrong shit you did, but okay, we can do it.
Yeah, because you're trying to make it seem like I'm jumping out bees with bees and nothing.
I never accuse you of that.
I don't say nothing.
You say you want a great kid to all types of shit.
And you said you need context of that.
You forgot.
You brought up a clip that I didn't know what the fuck you were talking about, a question.
You don't know what Rob Roxson says, R.G.
You covered that nigga before, no, all right.
I've never covered Rob Roxson and covered Jimmy.
I don't know what's so hard about that to understand.
Yo, you're gross, man.
I don't know what flew up your ass this morning about me,
but whatever it is, I hope it gets read.
I'm sorry about you. You can read that energy.
Yeah, you keep saying that.
It's it you fucking
Now he's acting dumb fuck you. I would love to know who's behind
Hurt me
You were so fucking retarded it kills me what even is this all about what got you so upset Samman
Tell me where the bad man touch your no-no parts. Tell me what
Tell me where the bad man pushed you, Stan, man.
Tell me where the bad man puts you.
You know what, weird ol' niggas trying to kill.
No, that's weird.
Now, I got touched now.
Well, I mean, it's over for you on this morning.
Who hurt you?
I didn't fucking certainly did do anything to you.
Now, I got touched now.
Well, you're obviously very upset.
I'm just trying to figure out why.
But that's okay.
I'm just trying to figure out why you're so upset.
No, no, no.
That's not you.
You started some crazy shit before that.
I got touch.
That's weird.
Jimmy is my fucking content
Stop it. I want everyone in chat to realize that he fucking picked this fight no fucking reason at all
No reason at all. And yeah, you know what Sam in
That mask is slipping and people can see it.
A hundred percent, a hundred percent.
Alright, so pick that mask from the floor and pick it up.
Thank you, Groovy.
Excuse me, thank you, Groovy.
Latinos and Hispanics are white.
You should know that, by the way.
Why do you always need somebody to take an opinion?
Thank you, Jimmy.
I don't even look at the chat when I watch it.
I don't look at it, I just want to argue.
My team members and Hispanics are white.
I know you consider yourself a black man.
You're definitely not.
KK confirmed that if you know what I mean.
Wait, wait.
You're definitely not black, dude.
So let's just stop it.
Shot to the shot out
You picked this fight with me for no fucking reason at all
Because Kate mentioned something that happened between me and Vita that we laughed about all of a sudden you're not upset
You're that upset between something that happened to me and Bita a year ago that we laugh about all of a sudden that just really ticked y'all
Come on dude
Something to happen between me and Bita a year ago just really got under your skin out of nowhere
Say oh, I know something obviously isn't right
You're happy to be something you only got 35 over there. Hey, it's after the recap. I thought you didn't
Right I'll be wrong for the strike right I'll be running for a striker, right? I'm not a cop nigga. I'm not a cop
I'm not a cop nigga. I don't strike people
What are you even angry?
No, no, you're absolutely this has something to do with a grudge. Sam and has against me has nothing
I don't give a fuck
I'm taking breaks for the troll about you nigga. You could be on my panel or not
It's so funny dude, it's so funny
Can I ask you an honest-to-god question, do you think Juice, the show is mounted on them?
You think he's entertaining in any way?
You know what, fuck that?
No, no, you bring everybody else to the drama.
Like, I need to fight Juice Battle.
I didn't fight nobody, man. I fight man.
Stop it. You're accusing me of bringing people to drama?
Yes.
Of all people.
Oh, you said you blew up Jews.
You, all people, are you choosing me
of bringing people to drama?
You've got to be kidding me.
Did you really just say that?
You're choosing me of bringing people to drama?
I said, take attitude out.
Come on.
You were the king of this sloppy woman drama.
Who the fuck are you kidding?
Oh, jeez, I'm bringing you up.
I'll make him cry.
Sam, can you admit that juice is not entertaining at all?
I can't admit that, but you said I'm cooking for juice, my nigga.
And that's 100% live on my mother.
Someone gassed you up.
I don't know who it is.
I'm not cooking for nobody.
Someone gassed you up.
It's called weaponized retardation, Sam.
And right now, you are being the retard that's being weaponized.
I can try to find out as to why, but you don't want to share that.
I got it.
You can talk to juice yourself.
He's too much of a pussy.
At least you have balls.
I'll give you that.
You have balls that at least have a conversation.
I'm tired of niggas picking and choosing.
And I caught it.
Niggas simple.
I caught it.
Picking and choosing is real.
I keep brought up something that happened a year ago, and all of a sudden you're mad.
And I brung it up.
What's the power?
You're so fucking transparent. So transparent. Holy shit.
No, thank you.
Yes, it was hurtful. Yes, it was. You know why?
I can't even talk on my own panel. God bless America. That's why I gotta yell.
Can I stay?
Chris and Marie
Wasn't for you Chris Murray that said damn why beating on goal our RG Kate would have never said nothing
I got the whole shebang. He said it not you
What are you talking about dude, how to you shout to you Chris Murray you you're so full of shit
Why can't you just be a genuine guy?
Right
No, no, no, no, no, no, you fucking know I'm not genuine you lied on me and said I didn't hit you up about Rob
Rocks, I gave you everything about Rob Rocks. I hit you in your DM
Show me after we were talking about it
Before we talked about it
I'm just saying, because I didn't have to hit you up at all.
I said, hey, you don't know about Rob Racks.
Hold on, let me finish.
Let me finish.
You said you don't know about Rob Racks.
I hit you up with the information, which I know you
already know about Rob Racks.
I said, I don't care about Rob Racks.
Just like you don't care.
I'll tell you.
Right, but I'm not going to sit here and have to say argument the thousands fucking time
I hit you up about
I'm not gonna do the same for a thousand times
You can't you know what is we're RG before you step ground on me. I've been through the witch hunt nigga
I've been through the witch hunt. Have you want to fight?
There he is Kate was having a wholesome stream then this comment started all the drama w. Crystal Marie
Crystal she won't go at the people who went real life on her
The people that actually sent her stuff
She blames me for that and I'm telling you all my kids I never sent a fucking thing to you
I never had anything to do with it. I never instructed anyone to I never had any knowledge of it nothing
Nothing ever.
I trolled you when I said I was gonna send you,
you send your dad a book of your news.
I trolled you.
Do you think I'm gonna waste my time
to print off Nudes on a fucking book,
on fucking Shutterfly and send that out?
No, it was a troll and it was a troll a year ago.
Blackout dropped her address weeks before anyone else.
Yeah, I got her address from the original Doxers
when she was getting deliveries
before I ever put anything out.
But of course, this is all a year ago.
I don't have any proof of this.
This shit's all been convoluted
and blamed on me since then.
So we're just going to run with the narrative
that I docked her.
So that's why she got deliveries instead of the truth.
Because it's easier to blame me because I'm the big bad wolf and that's the truth.
I wish I would have documented this shit last year because it sure would come in handy.
But she she should have it all documented because she's the one who's gone to the police about it.
She knows.
She knows the timeline.
But it's easier to blame me.
I just, I'm over it. I'm over it. I took down the distasteful post beta. I should not have docked you.
I should not have threatened the shit with your dad.
I shouldn't have been calling you and putting your phone number out. Even though your phone number was already out, Barry put it out.
What really happened well, let's let's all blame it on on big bad Kate
She was so wet brain doing 24 hour plus streams no way she had perfect timeline of how it unfolded that is very true
That is a very true she was in the midst of her fucking binge drinking like no other
Welcome RG. What's up. Hey, I can wait a minute. I know people have been looking forward to this so you can. No, you're fine.
You're fine. Well, so Sam is going off in his discord, saying that apparently you outed me for sending stuff to beta and I think he's getting it confused. He's planning on covering it.
uh, you know blame you which is very silly I know it's not and he's going off like it's some big news
saying oh I cover everything like it's so fucking silly uh it just just to correct this you were
talking about the first time when I first met Vita right when Docs threw it all that because he's
making it seem that this last time around even though J dog fucking admitted to doing it
uh somehow you're outing me for doing that for whatever the fuck the reason so that's
i guess it's the next to do content and trying to read what he's what he writes in discord is
a chore by itself uh you know what he's getting it he's getting it twisted i was pointing out
that you had gone and beat it at one point in time yes that's no secret i just stream on it and
that
She can forgive you
That was my point not I know it was your point
But apparently they're running with the fact that the last time she got pieces of shit
That was apparently me and you're ratting me out for it, which is not even close to being true
I had nothing to do with that and again, she doesn't fucking admitted it
Yeah, you were talking about when we first met and then when she was
Yes, I even said the Janet and Rita's time
Yeah, I just wanted to clear that up because he's going nuts in his discord like who don't blame me blame
Trillin Kate. I'm like, what are you talking about? I?
Wasn't listening to it. That's not what was said. It's not even close to what was said
Oh, whatever.
Yeah, no.
Yeah.
Countless.
Bathory says J-Dog admitted to it several times.
Exactly.
Like talk about digging for content, dude.
Come on.
Come on, dude.
Blame Kate.
I just cover everything.
First, it says J-Dog admitted he sent the rat, or at least claimed he did.
Like, I- is that fucking, uh, ever, uh, BG- uh, BG- that's funny.
Yeah, it's on BG's head. It's the best thing I've ever put him to say before.
Well, yeah, he's trying to say that you outed me and you're putting the blame on me.
It's very fucking silly.
You know, I was listening to the whole thing. It was like, that's not what the fuck happened.
But let's see if he covers this part of the show.
I didn't even discuss the most recent time. That's not at all what I was talking about. I didn't think so
Again, J-Dog was fucking doing a victory tour for you know about the whole thing
So chairman probably won't go very well trying to blame RG for some shit when someone else already said they did it
I don't know. It's just kind of digging for content. It's not there
Kate, can we please stick to the topic? I did as someone in backstage wrote that I did say I could I'd be happy to wait until the troll
Is shit is over. No, you're fine. I didn't we are barely into it. It doesn't really this is just a small
Yeah, I just I don't know a man
They're like blame Kate. I just covered the content like don't be silly
Shit to fit a fucking narrative and that's and come up with content
We'll just be fair about it.
I'm pretty sure I specifically said the Janet and Bita shit.
Oh, it's no secret because Bita,
she likes to give everyone the benefit of the doubt
and she does root for the underdog.
So she said to herself, I'm riding her die for Jimmy.
That didn't work out very well,
but that was a long time ago.
And I liked Bita since then and I like you too.
And if it was up to me, both of you guys would get along.
So I don't know trying to find content on it. Nothing is pretty fucking silly to me, but do what you got to do. I guess I
Don't know I'm not gonna fucking whatever just like if you're gonna play that part Sam and play this part too, please
You know, I'm not gonna be suckered into being content for fuck sakes
Yeah, no, that's not at all.
You can get back to this bullshit.
Sorry to fucking interrupt it.
Appreciate you.
Thanks, RG. Have a good one.
You too, Mike.
Yeah, that's not at all what I was saying.
I wasn't even referring to the most recent time I was talking about.
I was just making an example that.
There was issues with.
She now has him wrenched. That's it. I didn't say he sent her anything. I didn't say he is responsible for anything
Go ahead and twist it. However, you want crime in I think it's funny. I'm weird. I'm weird for watching beta
But you're not weird for watching me and raging about it in discord
Crime in you're not weird. Okay. All right back to this clip
the silence think it's empty space think a quiet life means a fragile place no crowd around no
noise no show so they assume there's nowhere else to go they lean back start cutting corners slow
late replies let the effort go
No scenes, no warning signs, just a shift you missed between the lines
You thought it bent, you thought it stayed, but it was measuring the price you paid
noise just to feel alive don't need a crowd just to survive
That was a shocking.
Oh, why does he go out the side?
Yeah, he goes to the side car.
He goes to the side car.
Leave Bita alone.
Leave my Bita alone.
How Bita?
I'm with my Bita.
Leave her alone.
I haven't heard someone whine like that
since that Britney Spears guy,
and like, you know.
Leave Britney alone, remember that guy?
Oh my God, oh yeah.
So I mean, it's like, I just wanna, you know.
Not like you not like everybody doesn't know what he's like or whatever
But maybe hey Alexander, yeah, I mean, yeah, I did I don't know yeah
These are some good. I made some good little yeah
These are some good a clip site company with you know, let's go through one more time here. These were good
There we did that one I
Think I got it pretty
Right, I mean, I think I mean you can't really see the whole thing. But it's yeah, there's the ugeo
It's here, yeah
That those are okay, but yeah
Yeah, that's not good the beat the beat the beat it didn't come out quite quite perfect
But uh, I tried my best it was a quick it was a quickie
Yeah, these kind of just they worked for the clip pretty pretty good
Yeah, well, I hope they they can just play play there and there's my RG
You know, it's not the same dog, but you know, I tried my best
But I'd say the RG that was definitely a W. You know, cheers to you for staying
You know calm under pressure
Well, not even under pressure. It's like, you know talking to Sam and it's kind of like
You know
Well, you know when you know, you know, it's like saving me. Yeah
So, I mean gosh, here's miss Lenore
Yeah, Lenore. But yeah, I had a, it was a good conversation today. And it's like, guys, if you think you know, like, like what's going on, I mean, I would say, check out the IP2 wiki today with Brandon and I and Alexandra because I think we're all like pretty much very objective people and, and fair and
There's stuff going on in the situation and it's like even like today
I like it's like now it's kind of like you know
There's always like these missing pieces to it and it's like I and never got it out once
But then seeing some of the clips today that I see like some of them literally of the clips are
Of him are are on AI that this Australian guy that used to be a scandal them
Gamble's a partner or something like that on on his show. There's co-host or something like literally
He and a lot of them are out of context and it's like basically just to
You know attack them and stuff like that. There's it would be yeah, I would say
It is sad because you know, I think it it
You know, it did really
I really heard him, but one good thing is that I think they sent like a hundred bots to his chat a day to like
To get his channel taken down and it ended up getting him monetized
Right and so it's like sometimes, you know, the evil done to us will turn into positive positive things
That's a good lesson like um, and so always like have good intentions
Would I ever like go after anybody like an IRL and or oh, okay, even in this guy that's been doing it to me for like over a year
it's like I just feel sorry for more than like I want to like get revenge on him I don't know.
And you know
it's crazy it's crazy but there's more to the story than you think and it's like and just like you
know seeing the pieces come together is pretty cool and it's also able it's good I feel good because
You know, I've had this done to me before or you know, and still I'm having it done to me and you know and
By like these like so many of these people are just bullies and are just sheep and
following the popular thing and everything and
you know
Believe everything they're told and stuff and so it's great to have some
very like some great objective journalism done, right?
kind of
Me and needs it needs it and not a lot of people are brave enough to
to
Go against the crowd, you know, and so here's to like Alexandra
You know, I don't know I don't know why
He's so desperate to get, you know, I don't know it's romantic to anybody how he's like just like, you know
Why are you doing a beta? I'm all about I mean, what would it be?
I think beta had like a one like one bag of concrete a pizza and
and uh, you know
What else I think, you know, and she literally cried every time that happened, you know, and it's like I never cried when that happened
I just you know
It's my thousands of pounds of concrete or whatever. I just was like, you know
I felt sorry for the people that were doing that madly in love with beetle
Maybe it's a love story for the ages guys the love story for the ages, but uh, I'll be back. I'll be back soon
I'm just gonna go get get some cigars and a couple drinks and maybe it's gonna eat and I'll be back later
I love you guys
Thank you. I'll be on this channel for a while. Okay. I'll talk to you soon
Bye guys.
See you soon.